## Seshadri Sastry Kunapuli

Manager Technology (Al&ML) seeking roles in Project Management ,Data Analysis,Data science,Machine Learning Algorithms,Research Analysis,Data Modeling,Predictive Modelling ,Python, MySQL ,Oracle, speech recognition, voice recognition,deep learning

- Current Designation: Manager Technology (Artificial Intelligence & Machine Learning)
- Current Company: Xinthe Technologies
- Current Location: Visakhapatnam
- Pref. Location: Delhi, Delhi / NCR, Gurgaon
- Functional Area: Analytics & Business Intelligence
- Role: Head/VP/GM Analytics & BI
- Industry: IT-Software/Software Services
- Marital Status: Married
- Total Experience: 15 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
- Notice Period: 1 Month
- Highest Degree: Ph.D/Doctorate [Machine Learning]
- Key Skills: Data Science, Deep Learning, Computer Vision, Machine Learning, Artificial Intelligence, Pattern Recognition, Image Processing, Signal Processing, Algorithm Development, voice recognition, python, SQL, recommendation system, Management, Project

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

ID: 0196ef52240b916a74Last Active: Jul-Sep 2020Last Modified: Jul-Sep 2020

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Projects |

Summary

Ph.D. (Computer Science & Systems Engineering) with ten years of experience in proficiency in designing predictive, adaptive & continuous solutions to assist in identifying new & emerging risk areas using advanced analytics and machine learning/ Artificial Intelligence techniques \* Thirteen patents applied in Artificial Intelligence. \* Excellence in developing advanced algorithms to solve problems of large dimensionality in a computationally efficient and statistically effective manner \* Skills in designing, developing & implementing analytical techniques on large, complex, structured & unstructured data sets (including Big Data) to facilitate clients in taking decisions \* Expertise in Development & Research; managing research programs, developing proposals for grants, planning & leading research programs followed by publications and patenting \* Resourceful in implementing statistical & data mining techniques such as hypothesis testing, machine learning

Work Experience

•

Xinthe Technologies as Manager Technology (Artificial Intelligence & Machine Learning)
Feb 2020 to Till Date

•

Al Xvidia Technologies PVT ltd as Lead Scientist Oct 2017 to Feb 2020

•

Goeventz as Consultant Data Scientist

Jan 2017 to Oct 2017

•

IEE as Prometeo Scientist
Oct 2014 to Oct 2015

^ Back to Top

## Education

- UG: B.Tech/B.E. (ELECTRONICS AND COMMUNICATIONS ENGINEERING) from gulburga university in 2001
- PG: M.Tech (Very Large Scale Integration Design and Embedded Systems) from Bharat Institute of Higher Education & Research, Chennai India in 2005

- Post PG: Ph.D/Doctorate (Machine Learning) from Andhra University, Visakhapatnam India in 2012
- Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Prometeo (Post Doctoral) Fellowship

^ Back to Top

**IT Skills** 

Skill Name Version Last Used Experience

Deep learning

Machine Learning Algorithms

Data Mining

Python, Java, C, MySQL

Oracle, MATLAB, GNU Octave, Kannel

Flask, Hadoop MapReduce, Spark

HTML 5, CSS, Javascript

TensorFlow, Deep Neural Networks

Real-World Problem-Solving

Reinforcement Learning, Q-Learning

Algebra, Calculus

Model Fitting and prediction

**Decision Trees** 

Regression, Neural Networks

Support Vector Machines, Naive Bayes

K-Nearest Neighbors, Adaboosting

Xilinx, Raspberry Pi, Embedded Systems

Linux, Ubuntu, Windows

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language Proficiency Read Write Speak

English

Hindi

Telugu

spanish

^ Back to Top

## **Projects**

•

Project Title: Automatic Categorization of EventsClient: GoEventz

o Nature of Employment: Full Time

o Project Location: Gurugram

o Role: Project Leader

o Duration: May 2017 - Sep 2017

o Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

o Team Size: 2

Skill Used: Natural Language Processing, un-supervised learning, embeddings, deep learningsklearn, Project Details: Clustering events based on their description, title, venue etc

•

Project Title: User Recommendation SystemClient: GoEventz

o Nature of Employment: Contractual

o Project Location: Gurugram

o Role: Project Leader

o Duration: Jan 2017 - Sep 2017

o Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

o Team Size: 2

Skill Used: collaborative filtering, recommender systems, supervised learning, KNN, sklearnProject Details: 1.To predict interesting events to customers based on their purchase history